Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Photographs and Audio-Visual Materials. PHOTOS.240
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Contact Sheets, 1964-2004.
  - Subseries III-A: Contact Sheets (that have matching prints), 1964-2000.
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "Much Ado About Nothing" (produced by National Players), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 574)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "One Mo' Time" (produced by American Theatre Wing), Oct 23, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 575)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees, Jun 22, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 576)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees, Apr 24, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 577)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees, Apr 4, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 578)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Brendan Byrne (Governor of New Jersey), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 579)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Gloria Swanson, Jan 18, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 580)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Gwen Verdon, Oct 23, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 581)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: John Strasburg, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 582)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Robert Morse and Maureen Stapleton, Dec 11, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 583)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Unidentified Russian Folksinger, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 584)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Alex H. Cohen and Hildy Parks, May 1985 (Box 9, Folder 585)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Armina Marshall, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 586)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Danny Kaye and Richard Rodgers (Central Park), Apr 1971 (Box 9, Folder 587)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Debbie Reynolds, Feb 2, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 588)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Ethel Merman, Oct 1971 (Box 9, Folder 589)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Joseph Papp, Apr 17, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 590)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Neil Simon, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 591)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: The Shubert Organization, Bernard Jacobs and Gerald Schoenfeld, Nov 18, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 592)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Vincent Sardi (photocopy of oversize contact sheet), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 593)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Warren P. Munsell, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 594)
    - Actors' Fund Women's Committee Lunch, Oct 19, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 595)
    - Actors' Work Program: Unidentified Event Shot by Jerry Speier, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 596)
    - "Annie" Christmas Party, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 597)
    - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 598)
    - Annual Meeting, undated (Box 9, Folder 599)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for), 1987 (Box 9, Folder 600)
    - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers: Luncheon and Tour of Actors' Fund Home, May 11, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 601)
    - Auction, Apr 1973 (Box 9, Folder 602)
    - Auction: Nearly New Shop, 802 Ninth Ave, New York City, undated (Box 9, Folder 603)
    - Auction: Sotheby Parke Bernet Theatrical Memorabilia, Apr 12, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 604)
    - Barney's, Actors' Fund Party at, Sep 24, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 605)
    - Barrymore Stamp Commemoration, Jun 8, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 606)
    - Bazaar, Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 607)
    - Bazaar, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 608)
    - Beck, Louise: Birthday Party, Feb 1977 (Box 9, Folder 609)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday) (folder 1 of 2), Jun 1987 (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday) (folder 2 of 2), Jun 1987 (Box 9, Folder 611)
    - Benefit Performance: "Anything Goes": Champagne Reception with Company, Apr 17, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - Benefit Performance: "Bon Apetit" (with Jean Stapleton), Nov 11, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Christmas Carol", Dec 12, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 614)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Christmas Carol", 1990 (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - Benefit Performance: "Uncle Vanya", Jul 29, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - Benincasa, Joseph P. (Executive Director), 1992 (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 618)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - Bloodbank/Blood Drive, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 622)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Canastel's 25th Annual Dinner for Nedda Logan Harrigan, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 624)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Midwest, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 625)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Shubert Alley, Aug 18, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 626)
    - Board of Trustees, undated (Box 9, Folder 627)
    - Bread Basket Campaign: Launching at Pub Theatrical, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 628)
    - Directors' Guild: Picnic, undated (Box 9, Folder 629)
    - Drama Desk Luncheon: Salute to Old Stars, May 16, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 630)
    - Duncan, Pamela and Tessie Marino Richner, undated (Box 9, Folder 631)
    - Fraunces Tavern: Boxing Day Dinner Party, Dec 26, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 632)
    - Gala, Nov 2, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 633)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I: Announcement at Cocktail Party, Helmsley Palace, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 634)
    - Gala: "That's Entertainment": Staff Photographs, Oct 2004 (Box 9, Folder 635)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington DC: Dinner at Statuary Hall, Oct 4, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 636)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Event at Washington Hilton, Oct 5, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 637)
    - Jacobson, Stuart: Book Party at Macy's for "Only the Best: A Celebration of Gift Giving in America", Nov 13, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 638)
    - McCarthy, Frances, Party for, Mar 18, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 639)
    - Office Staff: California Office, undated (Box 9, Folder 640)
    - Pataki, George (Governor of New York): Signing of New York State Legislature Bill (pertaining to actors' health coverage), Sep 13, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 641)
    - Perry, Blanche Collins and Luther Perry, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 642)
    - RAI, Italian Television Presentation of Check to Actors' Fund, Mar 3, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 643)
    - Simon, Louis M.: Retirement Dinner, Blood Award and Headshot, undated (Box 9, Folder 644)
    - Unidentified Event: "The Women" (b&w), Jul 17, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 645)
  - Subseries III-B: Contact Sheets (that do not have matching prints), 1969-2004.
    - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 646)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Dedication of Lillian Ferris Booth Room, Oct 1991 (Box 9, Folder 647)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Dedication of Lon Clarke Room, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 648)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 1990 (Box 9, Folder 649)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 650)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Percy Williams Wing, undated (Box 9, Folder 651)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Actors' Equity, Dec 20, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 652)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Warren P. Munsell, May 11, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 653)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 654)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame", 2000 (Box 9, Folder 655)
    - Blood Bank/ Blood Drive, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 656)
    - Brooks Atkinson Theater: 50th Anniversary, undated (Box 9, Folder 657)
    - "Educating Rita" (Invitational Screening), undated (Box 9, Folder 658)
    - Minnelli, Liza (performing at unidentified event), undated (Box 9, Folder 659)
    - Office Staff: Studio Portraits, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 660)
    - Survival Jobs Program: Party, undated (Box 9, Folder 661)
    - Unidentified, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 662)
    - Unidentified: Publicity Photographs Prudential Financial Inc. Sent to Rogers and Cowan Public Relations Firm, Jul 7, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 663)
    - Willard Swire Scholarship Award Ceremony, Oct 7, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 664)
- Series IV: Negatives, 1892-2001., 1970-2000
  - Subseries IV-A: Negatives (that have matching prints), 1892-2001., 1970-2000
    - Actors' Fund Art Gallery: Photographs of Artwork I, undated (Box 9, Folder 665)
    - Actors' Fund Art Gallery: Photographs of Artwork II, undated (Box 9, Folder 666)
    - Actors' Fund Art Gallery: Photographs of Artwork III, May 1985 (Box 9, Folder 667)
    - Actors' Fund Fair: Program and Press (copy photographs), 1892-1917 (Box 9, Folder 668)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Christmas Party, Dec 15, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 669)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Artist Rendering of Interior, undated (Box 9, Folder 670)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Founder's Day Picnic, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 671)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Founder's Day Picnic, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 672)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Floor Plan (copy photographs), undated (Box 9, Folder 673)
    - Actors' Fund Home, Staten Island, New York: Official Opening (with Joseph Jefferson as main speaker), May 5, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 674)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees, undated (Box 9, Folder 675)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Brendan Byrnes (Governor of New Jersey): Negatives, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 676)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Alex H. Cohen and Hildy Parks; Close-up of Medal, May 1985 (Box 9, Folder 677)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: The Shubert Organization, Bernard Jacobs and Gerald Schoenfeld, Nov 18, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 678)
    - "Annie" Christmas Party, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 679)
    - Auction, undated (Box 9, Folder 680)
    - Bazaar, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 681)
    - Bazaar: Alfred Lunt Display Window, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 682)
    - Bazaar: B-Group, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 683)
    - Bazaar: Booths, undated (Box 9, Folder 684)
    - Bazaar: Display Window, undated (Box 9, Folder 685)
    - Beck, Louise, undated (Box 9, Folder 686)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Shubert Alley, Aug 18, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 687)
    - "A Christmas Carol": Reception at Sardi's Restaurant, New York, Dec 15, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 688)
    - Cohan, George M.: Presentation of Donation to Actors' Fund; Award Plaque, 1919, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 689)
    - Duncan, Pamela and Tessie Moreno Richner, undated (Box 9, Folder 690)
    - Gala: Annual Holiday Gala, Dec 11, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 691)
    - Hagman, Larry (Trustee), undated (Box 9, Folder 692)
    - Lunt Fontaine Theater, Renaming of, undated (Box 9, Folder 693)
    - McCarthy, Frances, Party for, Mar 18, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 694)
    - McGlinn, Frank C. P. (Trustee), undated (Box 9, Folder 695)
    - O'Connor, Nancy (Trustee), undated (Box 9, Folder 696)
    - Office Staff: Dan and LeRoy's Going Away Lunch, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 697)
    - Office Staff: Megan's Baby Shower, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 698)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Exterior and Interior, undated (Box 9, Folder 699)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Opening, Nov 1998 (Box 9, Folder 700)
    - Physician Volunteers for the Arts: Lecture: Unprocessed Film (Kodak Advantix 400 format), Mar 13, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 701)
    - Streamers Softball in San Francisco, undated (Box 9, Folder 702)
    - Tremaine Twins (Edna & Evalin Burnett): Publicity Shots, undated (Box 9, Folder 703)
    - Trevor, Claire, undated (Box 9, Folder 704)
    - Vincent, Walter (President), undated (Box 9, Folder 705)
    - Wagstaff, Joseph, undated (Box 9, Folder 706)
    - Wolfington, Iggie (Trustee), undated (Box 9, Folder 707)
  - Subseries IV-B: Negatives (that do not have matching prints), undated.
    - Actors' Fund Home: Aerial Views of Complex, undated (Box 9, Folder 708)
    - Aurora Residence, New York City, undated (Box 9, Folder 709)
    - Bazaar, undated (Box 9, Folder 710)
    - Board of Trustees: Unidentified, undated (Box 9, Folder 711)
    - Hackett, James K., undated (Box 9, Folder 712)
    - Logan, Nedda Harrigan, undated (Box 9, Folder 713)
    - Reeves, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 714)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 9, Folder 715)
- Series V: Color Slides, 1977-1991.
  - Subseries V-A: Color Slides (that have matching prints), 1985-1991.
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 1988 (Box 10, Folder 716)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Edwin Forrest Day, Apr 1991 (Box 10, Folder 717)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Dedication Ceremony, Dec 15, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 718)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday), Jun 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 719)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Christmas Carol", Dec 12, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 720)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars II, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 721)
    - RAI, Italian Television: Presentation of Check to Actors' Fund, Mar 3, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 722)
    - Takarazuka Revue Company at Radio City Music Hall, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 723)
  - Subseries V-B: Color Slides (that do not have matching prints), 1977-1990.
    - Actors' Fund Home, Englewood, New Jersey, Mar 1982 (Box 10, Folder 724)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Interior and Exterior, undated (Box 10, Folder 725)
    - Father's Day Brunch (Harrigan Award to Lloyd Bridges) (folder 1 of 3), Jun 1989 (Box 10, Folder 726)
    - Father's Day Brunch (Harrigan Award to Lloyd Bridges) (folder 2 of 3), Jun 1989 (Box 10, Folder 727)
    - Father's Day Brunch (Harrigan Award to Lloyd Bridges) (folder 3 of 3), Jun 1989 (Box 10, Folder 728)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars III: Stage Shot of All Participants, May 5, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 729)
    - Ruehl, Mercedes: Neil Simon's "Lost in Yonkers", 1993 (Box 10, Folder 730)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 10, Folder 731)
    - Unidentified: Event in Memory of Alfred Lunt, Aug 1977 (Box 10, Folder 732)
- Series VI: Transparencies, 1982-1985.
  - Actors' Fund Home: Aerial Views of Complex, undated (Box 10, Folder 733)
  - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I: Stage Shot of All Participants, Feb 1982 (Box 10, Folder 734)
  - Gala: Night of 100 Stars II, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 735)
- Series VII: Postcards, undated.
  - Postcard: Actors' Fund Home, Englewood, New Jersey (b&w), undated (Box 10, Folder 736)
  - Postcard: Percy Williams Home, Long Island, New York (color), undated (Box 10, Folder 737)
- Series VIII: Oversize Photographs and Contact Sheets, 1926-1981.
  - Actors' Fund Home, Dinner at (panorama), 1927 (Box 11)
  - Actors' Fund Home: Exterior, undated (Box 11)
  - Actors' Fund Home, Staten Island, New York, undated (Box 11)
  - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Vincent Sardi, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Buck, George [? captions read "Gene"]: Testimonial Dinner (Catholic Actors Guild) (two b&w photos), May 2, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Cohan, George M.: Testimonial Dinner (Catholic Actors Guild), Apr 24, 1938 (Box 11)
  - Marshall, Armina (Trustee), 1981 (Box 11)
  - Palmer, Lili (photograph donated by Charlet Oberley), undated (Box 11)
  - Rathbone, Basil: Wedding Photographs, Apr 18, 1926 (Box 11)
  - Tremaine Twins (Edna and Evalin Burnett): Production Publicity Shots, undated (Box 11)
  - Unidentified Event: "The Women" (color) (Box 11)
  - Unidentified Portrait (signed to E. A. Meiser from "Bing"), May 7, 1934 (Box 11)
- Series IX: Scrapbooks, 1919-1992.
  - Actors' National Memorial Day, 1919 (Box 12)
  - Basil Rathbone, European Travels, mid-1930s (Box 13)
  - Edna Burnett, 1920s (Box 14)
  - George W. Moore, 20th Anniversary of Ordination, 1942-1975 (Box 14)
  - Night of 100 Stars I, Vol. 1, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Night of 100 Stars I, Vol. 2, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Parade of Stars, Palace Theater, New York, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Parade of Stars, Vol. 1, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Parade of Stars, Vol. 2, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Night of 100 Stars II, Vol. 1, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Night of 100 Stars II, Vol. 2, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Night of 100 Stars II, Vol. 3, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Night of 100 Stars III, Vol. 1, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Night of 100 Stars III, Vol. 2, 1990 (Box 21)
- Series X: Videotapes, DVD's and Film, 1910; 1981-2006.
  - Subseries X-A: Interviews and Television Programs, 1981-1990.
    - Asner, Ed and Jay Gerber: Los Angelos Actors' Fund Celebrity Blood Drive (VHS videocassettes; Channel 5 LA News), Oct 14, 1985 (Box 22, Item 1)
    - Dillon, Tom: Interview by Leonard Lief, Lehman College (VHS), May 25, 1990 (Box 22, Item 2)
    - Gish, Lillian: Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 3)
    - Gish, Lillian: Interview (3/4-inch U-matic video), undated (Box 22, Item 4)
    - Gish, Lillian and Helen Hayes: Interviews (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 5)
    - Hayes, Helen: Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 6)
    - Helen, Hayes: Interview (3/4-inch U-matic video), undated (Box 22, Item 7)
    - Hayes, Helen: "Happy Birthday Helen" WNBC Program "Prime of Your Life" (3/4-inch U-matic video), Jun 13, 1981 (Box 22, Item 8)
    - Kantor, Peppa: Ellis Island Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 9)
    - Keeler, Anna: Ellis Island Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 10)
    - Libin, Paul: Players Club Lucille Lortel Award (VHS), Mar 28, 1988 (Box 22, Item 11)
    - Logan, Nedda and Joshua: Dallas Tribute on the Today Show; NBC (VHS), Nov 17, 1986 (Box 22, Item 12)
    - Logan, Nedda and Joshua: Interview on the Today Show; "New York Views" American Theatre Wing; Chicago's "Shear Madness Benefit" (VHS), 1986 (Box 22, Item 13)
    - Scott, Willard: Today Show "Happy Birthday Mr. Abbott" (VHS), 1985 (Box 22, Item 14)
    - Sheppard, Marion: Ellis Island Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 15)
    - Stanley, Gary: Ellis Island Interview (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 16)
    - Vitelli, Vincent: Interview by John Sanders; "Our Town" Lyndhurst, New Jersey (VHS: Local Cable TV 3), undated (Box 22, Item 17)
    - A Chorus Line-Dance Program: Press Conferece on CNN Showbiz Today (VHS), Oct 1, 1985 (Box 22, Item 18)
    - "A Chorus Line Opening-The Actors Fund": CBS Morning News (VHS), Dec 10, 1985 (Box 22, Item 19)
    - Dance Program PR Event: Santigglia, Joanne on Channel 10 New Jersey (VHS), undated (Box 22, Item 20)
    - Actor's Fund on CNN and Etertainment Tonight (3/4-inch U-matic video), undated (Box 22, Item 21)
  - Subseries X-B: Actor's Fund Home, 1984-2000.
    - "Ground Breaking Actors Fund Home": Bentwood TV (3/4-inch U-matic video), Oct 23, 1984 (Box 22, Item 22)
    - "Ground Breaking Actors Fund Home": Bentwood TV (1/2-inch open reel video), Oct 23, 1984 (Box 22, Item 23)
    - "The Home": Documentary, External Footage of Complex (VHS), May 30, 1985 (Box 23, Item 24)
    - Actors' Fund Home Opening Ceremony (VHS), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 23, Item 25)
    - Actors' Fund Home Opening Ceremony (VHS), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 23, Item 26)
    - Actors' Fund Home Opening Ceremony (VHS), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 23, Item 27)
    - 2nd Annual Edwin Forrest Day: Channel 10 New Jersey (VHS), 1989 (Box 23, Item 28)
    - Edwin Forrest Day: Raw Footage-Liberty Studios (VHS), Apr 24, 1990 (Box 23, Item 29)
    - "Curtain Call": Documentary Short (DVD), 2000 (Box 23, Item 30)
    - Home Christmas Party: Four Interviews Combined (3/4-inch U-matic video), undated (Box 23, Item 31)
  - Subseries X-C: Benefits, Events and Miscellaneous, 1910; 1982-2006.
    - Actors' Fund Field Day-Silent Film (VHS), Aug 19, 1910 (Box 23, Item 32)
    - Actors' Fund Field Day-Silent Film (BETA), Aug 19, 1910 (Box 23, Item 33)
    - Night of 100 Stars: Channel 12 Tampa Florida (VHS), 1982 (Box 23, Item 34)
    - Night of 100 Stars II (VHS), 1985 (Box 23, Item 35)
    - "Stage for a Nation" (VHS), 1985 (Box 23, Item 36)
    - "A Chorus Line": Clip #1 (BETA), Oct 17, 1985 (Box 23, Item 37)
    - "A Chorus Line": Product Reel (VHS), 1985 (Box 23, Item 38)
    - "The Barrymore Incident" and "Stagecaoch Parade" (VHS), May 1987 (Box 23, Item 39)
    - PSA/USA Campaign: Sample Reel (1988) (Box 23, Item 40)
    - PSA/USA Campaign: Sample Reel; Rita Hayworth Gala Video Invitation; NY Film Festival 25th Anniversary Film (VHS), 1988 (Box 23, Item 41)
    - Broadway Magazine Promo Reel, Aug 1, 1988 (Box 23, Item 42)
    - Parade of Stars: Part 1 (VHS), Jun 24, 1991 (Box 23, Item 43)
    - Western Region Meeting: Slide Show (VHS), Sep 30, 1994 (Box 23, Item 44)
    - "Dreamgirls": 20th Anniversary Benefit Concert (DVD), Sep 21, 2001 (Box 23, Item 45)
    - "Funny Girl": Benefit (DVD), Sep 23, 2002 (Box 23, Item 46)
    - "Chess": Benefit (DVD), Sep 27, 2003 (Box 23, Item 47)
    - "Great Joy": A Holiday Celebration from Broadway (DVD), Dec 15, 2003 (Box 23, Item 48)
    - 4th Annual Benefit Concert: The New Amsterdam Theatre (DVD), Sep 20, 2004 (Box 23, Item 49)
    - Dillon, Tom: Memorial, Lambs Club with Barbara Primosch (DVD), May 17, 2005 (Box 23, Item 50)
    - "Charles Busch and Julie Halston: Together on Broadway": Benefit (DVD), Mar 28, 2005 (Box 23, Item 51)
    - "On the 20th Century": Benefit (DVD), Sep 26, 2005 (Box 23, Item 52)
    - "A Wonderful Life": Benefit (DVD), Dec 12, 2005 (Box 23, Item 53)
    - "Brian Stokes Mitchell and Friends: Broadway Sings the 60's": Benefit (DVD), 2005 (Box 23, Item 54)
    - Parade of Stars Featuring Karen Mason (DVD), Feb 6, 2006 (Box 23, Item 55)
    - "AIDS: Changing the Rules": AIDSFILMS (VHS), undated (Box 23, Item 56)
    - Canadian "Break a Leg" Awards (VHS), undated (Box 23, Item 57)
    - "There's No Business Like Show Business" (VHS), undated (Box 23, Item 58)
    - The Barrymores: Newsfeature (16mm Color Film, 120 seconds), undated (Box 23, Item 59)
    - DUB of All Beta Footage (VHS), Sep 30, 1990 (Box 23, Item 60)
- Series XI: Audiocassettes, 1986-1995.
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 1, May 1989 (Box 24, Cassette 1)
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 2, May 1989 (Box 24, Cassette 2)
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 1, May 15, 1990 (Box 24, Cassette 3)
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 2, May 15, 1990 (Box 24, Cassette 4)
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 1, May 21, 1991 (Box 24, Cassette 5)
  - Annual Meeting: Tape 2, May 21, 1991 (Box 24, Cassette 6)
  - Annual Meeting, May 25, 1995 (Box 24, Cassette 7)
  - Annual Meeting: 111th Meeting, undated (Box 24, Cassette 8)
  - Career Transition for Dancers Program: Gala Press Conference, Jun 25, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 9)
  - Career Transition for Dancers Program: Gala Press Conference, Jun 25, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 10)
  - Career Transition for Dancers Program: Wins News Conference, August 30, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 11)
  - Career Transition for Dancers Program: Wins News Conference, August 30, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 12)
  - Gish, Lillian: Chatanooga, undated (Box 24, Cassette 13)
  - Gish, Lillian: Tennessee Take 4, undated (Box 24, Cassette 14)
  - "Happy Birthday Mr. Abbott!" Act One, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 15)
  - "Happy Birthday Mr. Abbott!" Act Two, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 24, Cassette 16)
  - Meeting: Council or Board? (includes Colleen Dewhurst) Tape 1, undated (Box 24, Cassette 17)
  - Meeting: Council or Board? (includes Colleen Dewhurst) Tape 2, undated (Box 24, Cassette 18)
  - Meeting: Council or Board? (includes Colleen Dewhurst) Tape 3, undated (Box 24, Cassette 19)
  - Papoulis, James: First Earth Run Anthem, 1986 (Box 24, Cassette 20)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 1, Sep 8, 1993 (Box 24, Cassette 21)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 2, Sep 8, 1993 (Box 24, Cassette 22)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 1 (Duplicate), Sep 8, 1993 (Box 24, Cassette 23)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 2 (Duplicate), Sep 8, 1993 (Box 24, Cassette 24)
  - Western Council Meeting, Oct 6, 1993 (Box 24, Cassette 25)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 1, Jan 26, 1994 (Box 24, Cassette 26)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 2, Jan 26, 1994 (Box 24, Cassette 27)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 1, Jun 21, 1995 (Box 24, Cassette 28)
  - Western Council Meeting: Tape 2, Jun 21, 1995 (Box 24, Cassette 29)
  - Zale, Emma: "Always There", undated (Box 24, Cassette 30)
  - Zale, Emma: Pianist/Vocalist Demo Tape, umdated (Box 24, Cassette 31)
- Series XII. Artifacts, 1960-1970
  - Catholic Actors' Guild Plaques, 1960-1970 (Box 25)